[Music]
[Música]
Well, let's start with this if you don't mind
pues vamos a empezar por esto si os
because I really think that this
parece porque de verdad yo creo que esta
woman, this lady María Patiño,
mujer esta señora María Patiño
I think she's going nowhere. I think she
yo creo que va sin rumbo yo creo que
should leave Twitter. I do
debería dejar Twitter
n't know exactly what
No sé exactamente qué es lo que hace
this lady is doing with Twitter because she does
esta señora con el Twitter porque es que
n't use it professionally, in other
no lo utiliza de manera profesional o
words, they give María Patiño some very strange advice
sea le dan unos avenates muy raro a
on Twitter.
María Patiño en Twitter
Gloria Belén Esteban bores me Alicia,
Gloria Belén Esteban me aburre Alicia te
bores you Belén Esteban, my weapon Alicia, well,
aburre Belén Esteban mi arma Alicia po
send me a superchai, tell me what does
mándame un superchai dime qué es lo que
n't bore you and I'll sing to you and you'll like what does
no te aburre y te canto y te va a ir lo
n't bore you I promise I
que a ti no te aburra Te lo prometo Te
promise
lo prometo
but today Pilar also did a live show,
pero hoy también ha hecho directo hoy
man, with the campaign she
también Pilar hombre con la campaña que
did last night, you see, you can hear it low. Javi.
hizo anoche ya ves tú se oye bajo Javi
No, don't bring it up, kid, don't bring it up, gay, because I can
No no metanéis guaje no metan gay porque
hear it perfectly, I'm watching it
se oye perfectamente que lo estoy viendo
here. Do you think you have me?
yo aquí es que ustedes cree que me
Triana? Thank you very much for renewing, I don't know
Triana Muchas gracias por renovar no sé
if you're new members or if you're
si Son miembros nuevos o estáis
renewing, okay, listen to me. Do you
renovando vale escúchame Ustedes es que
think you can control me?  tangar and you
os creéis que a mí me podéis tangar y a
can't screw me you're so
mí no me podéis cangar que sois un
clever I have the gadgets right here in front of me I ca
astunante que yo tengo aquí adelante los
n't show them but I
cacharros no lo puedo mostrar pero yo
have the gadgets right here in front of me that
tengo aquí delante los cacharros que me
are telling me if you can hear them or not take a
están indicando si se escucha o no se
look around take
daros una vuelta
a look around I'm an astronaut can you
daros una vuelta que soy un astronauta
hear it well of course you can hear it well of course you can
se oye bien pues claro que se oye bien
hear it well let's
Pues claro que se oye bien
see what I was saying about María
a ver lo que iba diciendo de María
Patiño don't change the subject you
Patiño no me cambiéis de tema que me
're mentioning me there 1500 things in the
estáis mencionando ahí 1500 cosas en el
chat ask me in order Whatever you
chat preguntarme por orden Lo que
want but don't mix me up 800,000
queráis pero no me mezcléis 800.000
topics okay What does this mean María
temas vale Qué significa esto María
Patiño my soul what the [ __ ] is this María
Patiño mi alma qué [__] es esto María
Patiño you have to play guessing games
Patiño hay que jugar a las adivinanzas
every time you tweet something
cada vez que tuiteas algo
stay still already Damn Someone
estate quieta ya [__] Que alguien le
take this lady's [ __ ] Twitter away
quite el [__] Twitter a esta señora
Hi Javi from Castellón a kiss to
Hola Javi desde Castellón un beso para
all my people in Castellón I have to go
toda mi gente de Castellón tengo que ir
sightseeing to Castellón a kiss to all
de turismo a Castellón un beso para toda
my people in Castellón that you can't hear you
mi gente a Castellón que no se oye tú
want me to scream in your
quieres que te pegue un chillido en el
eardrum she'll see how  Hey Manu Jimenez do you
tímpano verá como lo Oye Manu Jiménez tú
want me to hit your
quieres que te pegue un sitio en el
eardrum with a hole you'll see how it goes? Listen to this what the
tímpano verás como lo Escucha esto qué
hell is this Maria Patiño what the hell
[__] es María Patiño esto qué [__]
is this that we have to be playing
es que hay que estar jugando a las
strategies with you and guessing games
estrategias contigo y a las adivinanzas
judicial strategies based on
las estrategias judiciales basadas en
sexist behavior should not
comportamientos machistas no deberían
be accepted bases accepted in
ser aceptadas bases aceptada en el
court whatever you come up with
juzgado lo que a ti te salga del [__]
Maria Patiño they're going to accept If you don't
María Patiño van a aceptar Si no sabes
even know journalism you're going to have to take
ni periodismo ya te vas a poner a clases
law classes too I mean the lady sends you
de derecho también o sea que te pone la
a tweet at 9 in the morning
tía aquí un tuit a las 9 de la mañana
plus she always tweets like very
además que siempre tuitea como muy a
late right I mean she tweets super
deshoras verdad O sea tuitea cosas súper
weird things now super weird
raras ahora súper rara
and also a paranoia in her head they're
y además una paranoia en su cabeza son
like reflections
como una reflexiones
what the hell is this
qué [__] esto las estrategias
judicial strategies based on
judiciales basadas en comportamientos
sexist behavior should not be accepted
machistas no deberían ser aceptadas
Maria Patiño you're going to have a trial for
María Patiño vas a tener un juicio por
defamation there
difamar
's no more machismo or feminism
no hay más ni machismo ni feminismo
realism as I told the lady Hey
realismo como le dije a la señora Oye
listen to me Right now they'll have to throw in the
escúchame Ya mismo tendrán que echar la
new hidden camera that I recorded they're
cámara oculta nueva que grabé es gente
wonderful people eh wow I see that wow
maravillosa eh lo vaya veo que
I see that he's
lo vaya veo que
going a lot, no
se le está yendo mucho no
booklet darling, he's going No, he's gone He's gone He's gone
cartilla cariño que se le está yendo No
completely, now he's
ya se fue Se fue Se fue por completo
gone, now he's gone I mean, he's not here anymore This is going without a
ya ya se fue ya O sea ya no está ya Esto
steering wheel This is going without a steering wheel
va sin volante Esto va sin volante
Javi in ​​Spanish speak well to the
Javi en español háblale bien a las
people the ladies who are squealing at you what's
personas a las señoras que te funan
really going on You've got me
que lo que mira de verdad qué pasa Me
fed up I'll rehearse for you it's that I
tenéis harto ya te ensayo yo es que me
spend all day wanting to come at
pego todo el día deseando venir por la
night in the afternoon and sometimes at night
noche por la tarde y yo a veces de noche
to see if it's nighttime already over there Go to
a ver si es de noche ya para allá Ve a
my wife At night there on the
mi señora Por la noche allí en el
telesarseo and when I arrive I sit in
telesarseo y cuando llego Me siento en
the chair that we've been live for 18
la silla que llevamos de directo 18
minutes I would send you to hell I would send you to hell
minutos os mandaba a tomar por culo os
Look, you know what they
mandaba a tomar por culo Mira sabes qué
criticize me on Twitter because they say that I since I
critican en Twitter porque dicen que yo
send the old lady to
ya que yo mando a la señora mayor y a
hell I
tomar por culo
swear there are people who believe that I mean it I
te lo juro que hay gente que se cree que
think they're people who hate me
yo creo que son gente como que me odian
and don't know what to hold on to since they
y no saben a qué agarrarse como no
have nothing to hold on to they
tienen nada lo que agarrarse
start making a sentence as if they were
se ponen a [__] frase como si se pone a
take my clips where I say that well no
[__] los clip míos donde yo digo eso
I don't like Javier Iveira
pues no A mí no me gusta Javier iveira a
I don't like Javier Oliveira I don't
mí no me gusta Javier oliveira a mí no
like being told to [ __ ] off go [ __ ] yourself [ __ ] you
me gusta que me manden a tomar por culo
're an idiot
que eres idiota
well he's not looking at the chat to
pues no está viendo el chat para
tell them to [ __ ] off
mandarlas a tomar por culo
Javi is angry because he's ready to
Javi está enojado porque está listo para
eat Nemo Oh well Hey, the subject doesn't mix with me,
papear a Nemo Ah bueno Oye no me mezcla
that's not here
el tema que eso no es aquí
María Patiño I really don't know
María Patiño que de verdad que yo no sé
what the [ __ ] you're doing at 9 in the morning, I
qué [__] hace tú a las 9 de la mañana o
mean at 9 in the morning I have such
sea a las 9 de la mañana tengo yo una
sleep in all my eyes that I can't even
lagaña en todos los ojos que no puedo ni
open my gun I have to put
abrirlo mi arma me tengo que echar a
apple on my eyelashes it wouldn't
manzana y ya en las pestañas a mí no se
occur to me at 9 and 7 in the morning to
me ocurre a las 9 y 7 de la mañana
tweet this stupidity
tuitear esta estupidez
[ __ ] is this judicial strategies
[__] es esto las estrategias judiciales
based on sexist behavior what
basadas en comportamientos machistas qué
sexist behavior And what
comportamiento machista Y qué
stupidity
estupideces
what sexist behavior girl you
qué comportamiento machista tía que te
made up all over your [ __ ] face to a
inventaste por toda la [__] cara a un
trial saying that there were cameras that
juicio diciendo que había cámaras que
had recorded Antonio Vi putting up the
habían grabado Antonio vi pegando los
posters and the poor guy doesn't even have enough left
carteles y el pobre no tiene ya ni para
photocopy the poor guy doesn't even have enough for a
fotocopia el pobre no tiene ya ni para
photocopy he was on his live show the other day
fotocopia estaba el otro día en su
saying oh this microphone that
directo diciendo ay este micro que me ha
Oliver Huerta gave me Oh here's this
regalado el Oliver Huerta Ay esta este
computer that my daughter gave me
ordenador que me ha regalado mi hija
these spotlights these spotlights that I
estos focos estos focos que me he
set up Here I am with the light from my cell phone and
montado Yo aquí con la luz del móvil y
the light from the nightstand lamp
con la luz de la lamparita de la mesita
this beach table that I opened
esta mesa de playa que la he abierto
here as best I could the poor guy was like this let's
aquí como he podido estaba el pobre así
see he doesn't have enough like someone who doesn't
a ver que no tiene para como el que no
have enough for a pipe
tiene para pipa
How could he have enough for a photocopy mother
Cómo va a tener para fotocopio madre
Patiño machismo not machismo
Patiño machismo ni machismo
[Laughter]
[Risas]
the macho strategies but imagine
las estrategias machistas pero imagínate
what he's referring to with this
a lo que se estará refiriendo con esta
nonsense
tontería
Imagine what he's referring to
Imagínate lo que se estará refiriendo
with this nonsense And this will
con esta tontería Y es que esto será
surely be Then it will surely
seguramente Entonces será seguramente
surely This will be that
seguramente Esto será que le habrá
some order will have arrived regarding this penalty
llegado algún auto del tema este penal
that he has and they'll be telling him
que tiene y le estarán diciendo
listen to me
escúchame
Don't laugh so sorry to Mercedes
No te rías tanto perdón a Mercedes
Sorry eh Sorry Mercedes Rivero that
Perdona eh Perdóname Mercedes Rivero que
Mercedes Mercedes Rivero got angry
Mercedes Mercedes Rivero se ha enfadado
because the joke that I made Mercedes
porque el chiste que he hecho Mercedes
which is a joke that I to me Antonio will
que es un chiste que yo a mí Antonio lo
take it here I will  My name is David, I call him
llevo aquí yo le llamo David yo le llamo
David Mercedes, don't get angry,
David Mercedes no te enfades
listen to me. It seems that
escúchame Esto será que le habrá llegado
a car has arrived, a car has arrived that
un auto que le habrá llegado un auto que
says, listen to me, Patiño, stop lying,
diga escúchame Patiño que deje de mentir
the press, you have, you have to
la prensa que tienes que
leave the 120,000 bucks here, she's
tienes que dejar por aquí los 120.000
totally crazy, totally these are very
está enajenada totalmente totalmente son
bad times to be on Twitter. Eva, these
muy malas horas para [__] Twitter Eva
are very bad times to be on Twitter, she
son muy malas horas para [__] Twitter
hasn't slept and is looking for an excuse.
no habrá dormido y anda buscando excusa
Listen to me, listen
escúchame
to me, Patiño, the
escúchame Patiño
best thing is that you don't get on Twitter
lo mejor es que no te pongas en Twitter
if you haven't slept, I'm
si no has dormido
telling you from experience.
te lo digo por experiencia
[Music]
[Música]